<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cloud Providers on Kube Docs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cloud Providers on Kube Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 16:16:16 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Azure EKS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/aks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/aks/</guid>
      <description>Optimize your AKS cluster management with KRS. This powerful tool, installed locally on your machine, analyzes your AKS cluster to identify areas for improvement. KRS leverages AI to provide recommendations for enhancing your cluster&amp;rsquo;s efficiency and functionality.&#xA;Ready to Get Started? Our comprehensive tutorial on our GitHub repository will guide you through Setting up Krs for an EKS cluster on Microsoft Azure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DigitalOcean</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/aws/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/aws/</guid>
      <description>Gain valuable insights for your DigitalOcean Kubernetes cluster with KRS. This local tool analyzes your cluster and provides recommendations for smoother management.&#xA;Ready to Get Started? Follow our guide on GitHub Installing and Configuring Krs with Digital Ocean Kubernetes Cluster</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS EKS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/eks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/eks/</guid>
      <description>Effortlessly optimize your EKS cluster with KRS. This powerful tool, running locally on your machine, analyzes your EKS cluster for improvement. Leverage KRS to gain valuable insights and recommendations for a smoother Kubernetes experience.&#xA;Ready to Get Started? Follow our step-by-step guide on Installing and Configuring Krs with EKS (AWS)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#39;s GKE</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/gke/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/gke/</guid>
      <description>Effortlessly optimize your GKE cluster with KRS. This powerful tool, running locally on your machine, analyzes your GKE cluster for improvement. Leverage KRS to gain valuable insights and recommendations for a smoother Kubernetes experience.&#xA;Ready to Get Started? Follow our step-by-step guide on Setting up Krs for Google Kubernetes Engine</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
