<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kube Docs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kube Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/getting-started/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/getting-started/overview/</guid>
      <description>KRS is an innovative AI-powered tool designed to simplify and streamline your Kubernetes cluster management. Imagine having an intelligent co-pilot for your cluster, offering insights and functionalities to optimize performance and maintain smooth operation. That&amp;rsquo;s exactly what KRS provides.&#xA;Why Use KRS? Effortless Optimization: KRS analyzes your Kubernetes cluster&amp;rsquo;s configuration and resource usage. Based on this intelligent assessment, it recommends the most suitable tools to address your specific needs, ensuring an optimized environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manual</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/tasks/manual/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/tasks/manual/</guid>
      <description>This is a placeholder page. Replace it with your own content.&#xA;Text can be bold, italic, or strikethrough. Links should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over).&#xA;There should be whitespace between paragraphs. Vape migas chillwave sriracha poutine try-hard distillery. Tattooed shabby chic small batch, pabst art party heirloom letterpress air plant pop-up. Sustainable chia skateboard art party banjo cardigan normcore affogato vexillologist quinoa meggings man bun master cleanse shoreditch readymade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Examples</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/examples/</guid>
      <description>This is a placeholder page that shows you how to use this template site.&#xA;Do you have any example applications or code for your users in your repo or elsewhere? Link to your examples here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure EKS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/aks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/aks/</guid>
      <description>Optimize your AKS cluster management with KRS. This powerful tool, installed locally on your machine, analyzes your AKS cluster to identify areas for improvement. KRS leverages AI to provide recommendations for enhancing your cluster&amp;rsquo;s efficiency and functionality.&#xA;Ready to Get Started? Our comprehensive tutorial on our GitHub repository will guide you through Setting up Krs for an EKS cluster on Microsoft Azure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DigitalOcean</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/aws/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/aws/</guid>
      <description>Gain valuable insights for your DigitalOcean Kubernetes cluster with KRS. This local tool analyzes your cluster and provides recommendations for smoother management.&#xA;Ready to Get Started? Follow our guide on GitHub Installing and Configuring Krs with Digital Ocean Kubernetes Cluster</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Desktop</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/tasks/docker-desktop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/tasks/docker-desktop/</guid>
      <description>This is a placeholder page. Replace it with your own content.&#xA;Text can be bold, italic, or strikethrough. Links should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over).&#xA;There should be whitespace between paragraphs. Vape migas chillwave sriracha poutine try-hard distillery. Tattooed shabby chic small batch, pabst art party heirloom letterpress air plant pop-up. Sustainable chia skateboard art party banjo cardigan normcore affogato vexillologist quinoa meggings man bun master cleanse shoreditch readymade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS EKS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/eks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/eks/</guid>
      <description>Effortlessly optimize your EKS cluster with KRS. This powerful tool, running locally on your machine, analyzes your EKS cluster for improvement. Leverage KRS to gain valuable insights and recommendations for a smoother Kubernetes experience.&#xA;Ready to Get Started? Follow our step-by-step guide on Installing and Configuring Krs with EKS (AWS)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kind</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/tasks/kind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/tasks/kind/</guid>
      <description>This is a placeholder page. Replace it with your own content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minikube</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/tasks/minikube/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/tasks/minikube/</guid>
      <description>Minikube is your key to unlocking a powerful local Kubernetes environment. This lightweight tool lets you set up a single-node Kubernetes cluster on your machine in a flash. It&amp;rsquo;s perfect for:&#xA;Learning Kubernetes: Gain hands-on experience with core concepts in a controlled setting. Testing Applications: Deploy and test your containerized apps locally. Rapid Iteration: Experiment and refine your configurations without impacting production. Ready to dive in? Check out our comprehensive Minikube tutorial for a step-by-step guide: Install and Configure Krs with MiniKube</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contribution Guidelines</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/contribution-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/contribution-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the world of KRS contributors! We&amp;rsquo;re excited to have you join our mission of empowering users with a seamless Kubernetes experience. This guide outlines how you can make valuable contributions to the KRS project.&#xA;Sharpen Your Skills Kubernetes Expertise: Possessing a strong foundation in Kubernetes concepts allows you to understand user needs and tailor contributions accordingly. KRS Functionality Deep Dive: Delving into KRS functionalities equips you to contribute to core functionalities, integrations, or even documentation improvements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How It Works</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/getting-started/how-it-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/getting-started/how-it-works/</guid>
      <description>The Kubernetes Resource Scanner (KRS) utilizes a multi-faceted approach to empower you with intelligent Kubernetes cluster management. This section delves into the core functionalities and the underlying Artificial Intelligence (AI) mechanisms that drive KRS&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness.&#xA;Comprehensive Cluster Analysis Initial Scan: Upon executing krs scan, KRS conducts a comprehensive scan of your Kubernetes cluster. This scan meticulously identifies the tools currently deployed within your environment, providing valuable insights into your existing infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Architecture</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/getting-started/architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/getting-started/architecture/</guid>
      <description>This is a placeholder page. Replace it with your own content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLI Reference</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/cli-reference/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/cli-reference/</guid>
      <description>The KRS CLI provides a powerful set of commands for interacting with your Kubernetes clusters and leveraging KRS&amp;rsquo;s intelligent features. This section serves as a comprehensive reference guide for all available commands and their functionalities.&#xA;krs --help Usage: krs [OPTIONS] COMMAND [ARGS]... krs: A command line interface to scan your Kubernetes Cluster, detect errors, provide resolutions using LLMs and recommend latest tools for your cluster ╭─ Options ─────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────╮ │ --install-completion Install completion for the current shell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Example Page</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/getting-started/example-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/getting-started/example-page/</guid>
      <description>This is a placeholder page. Replace it with your own content.&#xA;Text can be bold, italic, or strikethrough. Links should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over).&#xA;There should be whitespace between paragraphs. Vape migas chillwave sriracha poutine try-hard distillery. Tattooed shabby chic small batch, pabst art party heirloom letterpress air plant pop-up. Sustainable chia skateboard art party banjo cardigan normcore affogato vexillologist quinoa meggings man bun master cleanse shoreditch readymade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
