<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Local Installation on KRS Docs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/tasks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Local Installation on KRS Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 13:41:18 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/docs/tasks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Manual</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/tasks/manual/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/tasks/manual/</guid>
      <description>This is a placeholder page. Replace it with your own content.&#xA;Text can be bold, italic, or strikethrough. Links should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over).&#xA;There should be whitespace between paragraphs. Vape migas chillwave sriracha poutine try-hard distillery. Tattooed shabby chic small batch, pabst art party heirloom letterpress air plant pop-up. Sustainable chia skateboard art party banjo cardigan normcore affogato vexillologist quinoa meggings man bun master cleanse shoreditch readymade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Desktop</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/tasks/docker-desktop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/tasks/docker-desktop/</guid>
      <description>Get started with Docker Desktop to build and run containerized applications.&#xA;To install and get started with Docker Desktop, follow these steps:&#xA;Download the installer: Visit the official Docker website to download the appropriate installer for your operating system (Windows, macOS, or Linux).&#xA;Run the installer: Execute the downloaded installer and follow the on-screen instructions to complete the installation process.&#xA;For detailed instructions and troubleshooting, refer to the official Docker documentation: Instructions on Getting Started</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kind</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/tasks/kind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/tasks/kind/</guid>
      <description>This is a placeholder page. Replace it with your own content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minikube</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/tasks/minikube/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/tasks/minikube/</guid>
      <description>Minikube is your key to unlocking a powerful local Kubernetes environment. This lightweight tool lets you set up a single-node Kubernetes cluster on your machine in a flash. It&amp;rsquo;s perfect for:&#xA;Learning Kubernetes: Gain hands-on experience with core concepts in a controlled setting. Testing Applications: Deploy and test your containerized apps locally. Rapid Iteration: Experiment and refine your configurations without impacting production. Ready to dive in? Check out our comprehensive Minikube tutorial for a step-by-step guide: Install and Configure Krs with MiniKube</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
